Death was only the beginning.
A Haunting in Venice is a mystery, thriller, crime
film directed by Kenneth Branagh.
Celebrated sleuth Hercule Poirot, now retired and living in self-imposed exile in Venice,
reluctantly attends a Halloween séance at a decaying, haunted palazzo.
When one of the guests is murdered, the detective is thrust
into a sinister world of shadows and secrets.
Hercule Poirot, played by Kenneth Branagh.
Maxime Gerard, played by Kyle Allen.
Olga Seminoff, played by Camille Cottin.
Dr Leslie Ferrier, played by Jamie Dornan.
Ariadne Oliver, played by Tina Fey.
Leopold Ferrier, played by Jude Hill.
A Haunting in Venice is a 2023 British mystery film produced and directed by Kenneth Branagh from a
screenplay by Michael Green, loosely based on the 1969 Agatha Christie novel Hallowe'en Party.
The third instalment of the Hercule Poirot film series, it is a sequel to the 2017
film Murder on the Orient Express and the 2022 film Death on the Nile.
The ensemble cast includes Branagh reprising his role as Hercule Poirot, alongside Kyle Allen, Camille Cottin, Jamie
Dornan, Tina Fey, Jude Hill, Ali Khan, Emma Laird, Kelly Reilly, Riccardo Scamarcio, and Michelle Yeoh.
A Haunting in Venice premièred at the Odeon Luxe Leicester Square cinema in London on 11 September 2023, and was
subsequently released theatrically in the United States on 15 September by 20th Century Studios.
The film received positive reviews from critics and
grossed US$122.3 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, venice,
italy, loss of loved one, detective, medium.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.